[{"answer": "I bowed to Lady Gaga.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "You bowed to Lady Gaga?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, when I see him I call him Barack or President Obama or Mr. President.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "What do you call the president?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "I'm great, thank you.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "How do you do?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I am turning 21 in two weeks.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I have a fantastic publicity team.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How did you do this?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "No, no, I was just a student and I was in high school a few months before I got the show, and then I was in college for two weeks, and then when I officially got it and -- I was working at a dry cleaner's in the summers to --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "I mean, you weren't even -- you weren't doing anything before you got this job, were you?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I think it was -- oh, gosh!", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Earning how much?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, I was driving back from the last audition, and I was -- my mom, my mom was driving.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "-- about \"Glee\"?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "The look was -- like, it looked like she should be driving, she should be paying attention to the road.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "What's the look?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Did you have an inkling?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I literally cannot.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "I mean, who could've predicted all of this?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I think I --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Were you thinking in your head, \"I really want to be\" -- I don't know, whoever?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Tom Cruise, you know?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Definitely -- definitely not, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Zac Efron?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "No, I never thought I would ever be of heartthrob stature.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Who are your idols?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh!", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Who were your celebrity icons?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Well, not actually Oprah?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Yes, ever since -- I remember I was, like, 3 years old, and I was watching a movie, the title of which escapes me, but -- and I remember the credits came on.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Did you want to be an actor?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "When did it pop for you?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "The moment when you rang your mum and you were both getting carried away on the phone.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Oh, God -- what was the first \"pinch me\" moment?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "When I signed up for \"America's Got Talent.\"", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "I mean, the first day of filming the live shows was through those famous gates.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes, it's an amazing feeling, it is.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Now, that is a moment, isn't it?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Right, absolutely.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "It's just kids who feel they're outsiders, right?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I remember when I was walking up, I kept thinking to myself: do not trip on a chair or a table on the way up there, because it was so possible, because there were so many things in my way.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "But as you were walking up, you just thought -- what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Do you remember their names?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "No, I hated them all equally, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Is there anyone in particular that you'd like to just smoke out now?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I was just embarrassed, because -- I mean, I would walk by these people that I barely knew in the hallway, and they'd just scream profanities at me that I didn't think were true at the time.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "How did it make you feel?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "To me, she's just a phenomenon who completely gets what it takes to be a modern-day brand, doesn't she?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "A couple times.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Did you meet her when she came on?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Well, I completely embarrassed myself to no end.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What did you make of her?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I bowed to Lady Gaga.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "You bowed to Lady Gaga?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "\"Thank you.\"", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "No, I just ran.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Did you have to, then, do anything else?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "No, I don't think I'll ever be able to have a proper conversation with her after that.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Did you get to have a proper conversation with her?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I'd be way too -- yes, right.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "You'd be too nervous?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I -- you know, she's actually one of the first people in my generation whose music I liked.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Is she like an iconic figure for you?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Oh, everyone loves \"Glee.\"", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "I bet they're just all over you like a rash about \"Glee,\" right?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Well, here's the thing.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Do you ever say to them, \"I know how you voted\"?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "But do you think that they will ever change their mind because you give them a picture?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "You know who they are when they ask you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "And you know how they voted?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "I mean, do you feel like you're winning when you have that moment with them?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I don't know, because I know that I surround myself with positivity towards the situation and not negativity.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Or do you feel that as gay rights become much more prominent and successes are being achieved, in a funny way, it's becoming in certain pockets, more homophobic as they try and resist this change?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "It was just -- high school again.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "What kind of things?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Yes, because I mean, it's ridiculous when people have like strong opinions about you when it's about things you can't control.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "And that hurt?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Right, it comes --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "It's all hand-in-hand, isn't it?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "It's so funny.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What did your mother say when she saw this?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "It's what mothers do, isn't it?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Oh, sure.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "I mean, are you finding that you're getting more attractive because of the fame?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Kind of, kind of.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "It's like fame is such a sort of magnet to people, isn't it?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "That's -- yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "That goes with the territory, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you think you're -- are you equipped to deal with all this?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "You know, like the security risks and the security issues that are very frightening that people don't know about, because I don't want them to know about.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "And what's behind-the-scenes stuff with you?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I was at a movie theater once, and I was by myself, stupidly, and I was semi-mobbed.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "What's the scariest thing that's happened to you?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Not much.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "As it was going on, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "It's crazy, but I mean, in -- it's really a mind trip because, on one hand, you're -- you want them to stop.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "It was crazy, right?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Not -- not really.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Have you had stalkers?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Some form of stalking is flattering, you know?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "I mean, how can you trust people?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Life is a gamble.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Life's a gamble, though, isn't it?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "It's really just a -- kind of like a glancing.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "How do you get your tears to work?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Well, now.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Can you do it now?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on the scene.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "How long would it take you to get into tear mode?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "A minute.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "A minute?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I could, I could, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "You could get tears in a couple of seconds?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, not -- unless it's scripted.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Yes, right, that's --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Is it like a magician revealing his secrets?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "That's what it is.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "You're feeling awkward about it?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "No -- no, I mean it's -- no, because sometimes you just can't do it because your body can't produce tears, so you can't.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "To order?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I don't think I've cried --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "The last time I cried.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "When was the last time?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "So, you're not actually that emotional off camera?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "OLFER: Yes, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "All that bullying, all that ostracizing?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I think it made me a very sarcastic person, for sure.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "-- steelier side to you than you had when you were growing up?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "We finished season two yesterday at 4:00 in the morning.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "When did you finish working on this scene?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "And do you now get time off, or what happens?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "And you're also doing a movie in all this?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Well, the tour ends on July 5th or 4th, I believe, and as soon as it's over, I am literally going straight to a plane and flying to the set in LA.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "How are you going to fit that in?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Do you get any time off at all?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Maybe -- I'll get like a day here and there.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Even a day?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "That's it, right?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "There --", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Is there anything else you're up to, other than all this?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Or is that enough this year, is it?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Oooh.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Of all the famous people you've met, who's been the most inspiring to you when you actually met them?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "\"Hi, I'm Barack.\"", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "I think his daughters did.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Did he know you?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "No, no, he wasn't like, \"Oh, I loved you in 'Single Ladies.'\"", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "He didn't say he watched it religiously?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Great, great.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Yes, what was she like with you?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "A little bit, a little bit, a little bit, yes.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "So, your mother isn't getting demanding about fame, now, right?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "For some people it could be.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "I mean, that's a bummer, isn't it?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "I mean, are you proud to be Michelle Obama's older brother?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Are you amazed at how she's dealt with becoming first lady?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Well, the answer is nobody.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Who grows up on the south side of Chicago and, as you pointed out, very modest background, and ends up being the first lady?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "Oh, when I see him I call him Barack or President Obama or Mr. President.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "What do you call the president now, when you see him?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Doesn't it feel even stranger calling him Mr. President?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "You know, I had heard she was dating a guy who was a Harvard guy and they worked together in the summer and this, that, and the other.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "Had you heard of him before?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard when you get fatigued to shield your real personality.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Is it as simple as those things that he was doing means he's a good man?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "Oh, I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Well, I got to tell you, the first thing, Piers, that struck me was how small the inside of the White House was.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "What's the moment like for you personally, on a human level, when you walk into the White House for the first time with your brother-in-law as the president of the United States?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "It's a lot smaller than you think, isn't it?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "And it still is.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "But was it a surreal moment for you?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "You know, I would love to tell you that there was something that bothers me, but nothing that anybody says bothers me.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 860, "question": "Something that annoys you most when you see them described as whatever?", "qSentId": 859}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "You never did?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "Well, I have to say I was probably like most of the people who heard the news.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "How did you feel when you discovered that your brother- in-law had ordered the mission, the successful mission that killed Osama bin Laden?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Well, if they need me.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 885, "question": "And, finally, will you be out on the stump for him next election campaign?", "qSentId": 884}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110527pmt", "aSentId": 920, "question": "You're threatening me with physical violence, aren't you?", "qSentId": 919}]